<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on baArt</title><link>https://baartch.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on baArt</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 20:22:51 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://baartch.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Minority</title><link>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0007-minority/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 20:22:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0007-minority/</guid><description>When I saw the headlines today, it made me feel very sad and disappointed. Switzerland voted yesterday. We have made it illegal to wear a Burka. There are now dress codes in our law. How weird? Not that I never ever saw a women wearing one in Switzerland. So it&amp;rsquo;s not about preventing people covering their faces. It&amp;rsquo;s about discriminating a religion. It&amp;rsquo;s about stimulating fear of foreign cultures.
Further we declined the launch of an electronic Identity Document.</description></item><item><title>put a file on multiple S3 buckets asynchronous</title><link>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0006-asyncs3upload/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 19:23:33 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0006-asyncs3upload/</guid><description>Today I was trying hard to write a Lambda function, that deploys a file on multiple S3 buckets asynchronous. My problem was that the files were only uploaded every other time I ran the Lambda. Of course, this behavior suggests, that there was something wrong the Promises and/or the async/await combinations. Unfortunately, I still don&amp;rsquo;t understand the Promises completely. I once have to dive into it.
Finally, my script works. But it is unsatisfactory not understanding completely what&amp;rsquo;s going on.</description></item><item><title>CDK CodePipeline</title><link>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0005-cdkpipeline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 11:23:33 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0005-cdkpipeline/</guid><description>It took me almost a day to figure out how to fix a problem with deploying a pipeline with CDK. The build stage was alwayis running into an error:
[Container] 2021/03/01 08:02:29 Entering phase PRE_BUILD [Container] 2021/03/01 08:02:29 Running command npm ci npm ERR! archiver not accessible from aws-cdk npm ERR! A complete log of this run can be found in: npm ERR! /root/.npm/_logs/2021-03-01T08_02_34_128Z-debug.log [Container] 2021/03/01 08:02:34 Command did not exit successfully npm ci exit status 1 [Container] 2021/03/01 08:02:34 Phase complete: PRE_BUILD State: FAILED [Container] 2021/03/01 08:02:34 Phase context status code: COMMAND_EXECUTION_ERROR Message: Error while executing command: npm ci.</description></item><item><title>C'è un ottimo ristorante vicino all'edicolo.</title><link>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0004-vicino/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 20:52:33 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0004-vicino/</guid><description>Today I&amp;rsquo;m very thankful for having good friends. We were out in the forest for a walk and afterwards sitting in the park. We had very good conversations. It&amp;rsquo;s nice to hear how they&amp;rsquo;re really doing in these crazy times.
Tonight in my Italian practice I learned how to use the adjective vicino and how to conjugate the verb andare.</description></item><item><title>Svelte and the Great Space Elevator</title><link>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0003-svelte/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 20:24:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0003-svelte/</guid><description>After the speach of Shawn Wang at the JS World Conference this week, I had to watch his video called Svelte and the Great Space Elevator tonight. I absolutely can recommend it. But for now, I have nothing more to say, that I&amp;rsquo;m really curious about Svelte and its possibilities. I have to look into it&amp;hellip; You will find further links in his video description.</description></item><item><title>Allowed function parameters in TS</title><link>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0002-allowedfunctionparametersints/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 20:24:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0002-allowedfunctionparametersints/</guid><description>Today I learned two things. The first is how to create a function whose parameters only allow certain values. The key thing here is to create an enum and provide it as data type to the parameter.
The second thing may seems dilettante to you, but to me this was new. I learned how to document my JS code with JSDocs.
/** * available AWS resources */ export enum resourceType { codeCommitRepository = &amp;#39;ccr&amp;#39;, codePipelinePipeline = &amp;#39;cpp&amp;#39;, iamPolicy = &amp;#39;iamp&amp;#39; } /** * This function generates a name for a resource * @param resourceType - The resource type * @param name - name of the resource */ export function generateResourceName(resourceType: resourceType, name: string): string { return `${resourceType}-${name}`; }</description></item><item><title>My first post</title><link>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0001-my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 20:22:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://baartch.github.io/posts/0001-my-first-post/</guid><description>Hi there. This is my first blog post. Actually, I&amp;rsquo;ve got no clue what to achieve and where to end up with this blog. I&amp;rsquo;m doing just for myself. Kind of a diary. To document where this journey called life leads me to. To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m not even really sure about what the content is going to be about. I think I&amp;rsquo;m going to write down what ever keeps me busy.</description></item></channel></rss>